I don't have the
balance think I'm going to
fall wish I had the
talent I don't belong here at
[Music]
all drowning in the
pressure in over my head why did I think
I could do this
I could have walked away instead but
this is my chance to break free
everything's depending on me and if I
keep trying I'll be on top of the
world where I can see everything before
me reaching up to touch the sky on top
of the world all my dream all my
dreaming
me stretching on my wings to fly on top
of the wall where I can see everything
before me reaching up to touch the sky
on top of the world my dream all of my
dream are rushing toward me stretching
on my wings to fly on top of the
worldall a
[Music]